Emilio Hoffmann Corpus

1876 N. Forest Hill Pl., Danville, CA

emiliocorpus@gmail.com

Cell: 925-708-0062

Professional Summary

Full-stack web developer with expertise in **Ruby on Rails** and **Object Oriented Javascript**. Efficient problem solver, excellent collaborator and easily adaptable. Inspired to expand current programming capacities. Previous emergency room scribe with over two years experience in electronic medical records.

Qualifications

- Ruby On Rails
- HTML/CSS
- Relational Databases
- Github
- Frontend/Backend Design
- Heroku Deployment
- Experienced Peer Programmer
- Microsoft Office
- Windows and Mac Literate

- Javascript
- Jquery
- React.js
- · Git Workflow
- Test Driven Development
- Engineering Empathy
- Electronic Medical Records
- Medical terminology
- HIPAA

Professional Experience

Dev Bootcamp Coding School, San Francisco, CA, 2015

Dev Bootcamp is an immersive web development course that provides aspiring developers the skills to become life-long learners, team players, with a main focus in object oriented Javascript and Ruby on Rails

Teaching Assistant, 2015

- Refactoring and code reviews
- Mentor and guide students towards implementing best-practices
- Experience new mechanisms and strategies for solving certain problems

John Muir Medical Emergency Room, Walnut Creek, CA, 2012–2015

Emergency Room Medical Scribe, 2012–2015

- Create and manage physician chart templates
- Collaborate with physicians and other healthcare professionals to maintain an efficient workflow
- Compile, write and edit patient histories, physical exams, medical decision making
- Expert in chart workflow, HIPPA, hospital guidelines and regulations

University of California-Irvine, 2008-2012

Research Lab Assistant, Dr. Michael R. Rose, 2011

- Maintain lab setting and materials
- Dividing and organizing test specimens by gender

Education & Certifications

Bachelor of Science, Biology, University of California–Irvine, Irvine, CA 2012

Microbiology, Physiology, Cellular biology, Biochemistry, Organic chemistry, physics

19-Week Web Development, Dev Bootcamp, 2015

- Ruby / Ruby on Rails
- Javascript (Vanilla, Jquery, React.js)
- Engineering Empathy
- Peer programming
- Model View Controller Framework
- Objected Oriented Programming